question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Rapper Snoop Dogg&#039;s real name is &#039;Cordozar Calvin Broadus, Jr.&#039;.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The cover of The Beatles album &quot;Abbey Road&quot; featured a Volkswagen Beetle in the background.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The song &quot;Mystery Train&quot; was released by artist &quot;Little Junior&#039;s Blue Flames&quot; in 1953.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his &quot;Mothership&quot; set piece for one night only.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
                                       "question": "The singer Billie Holiday was also known as &quot;Lady Day&quot;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
